

Arthur Lynn E. Williams Web Developer

Contact

Phone

639453163943

Address 39D Insurance Project8 Quezon City Philippines

Email arthurlynnwilliams01@gmail.com

Expertise

Forex Trading

Account Management

Sales / Business

Development

Lead Generation

Customer Service

Fund Management Logistics

References

Sun Life Canada Von Montepiedra 639152342483

Security Bank
David Gio Dela Rosa
639178235163

Seda Hotle Jasmine Habulan 639559073432 Experienced Sales Specialist with years of expertise in different industries. Now I am shifting into a near career as a Web Developer. I am a full-stack web developer but has more focus and developed more skills in backed programming using Mongo DB

Educational

BS Hotel and Restaurant Management

Experiences

UNIRAMP July 2022-Present

Overlook & manage sales team activities in a specific area and/or for specific accounts

Maintain and provide a detailed and continuous sales report and forecast

Develop proposals, conduct sales conversations, give presentations

Actively understand each customer's strategic growth plans, technology, and needs Contacting potential clients via email and/or phone to establish rapport and set up meetings.

Lead a team to overlook and manage sales activities in a specific area and/or for specific accounts

Inxpress USA- Senior Sales Executive - Contractual

January-July 2022

Provide and assist the current clients with their shipping inquiries. Upsell existing services to existing clients. Generate more clients via cold calls and emails. Guide new clients on how to use the systems. Monitor and track shipping transactions both domestic and international

Nature Forex- Sales Account Manager - Contractual

September 2020- July 2021

Manage the entire sales process by identifying prospects via cold calling, email, and face-to-face. Develop the business and implement a sales plan. Generate own leads. Sell auto trading platforms and systems. Maintains updated professional and technical knowledge of Forex market information. Build relationships with current and future IBs to have more potential business. Do weekly webinars for new clients and potential clients to build a deeper relationship, interest, and knowledge in Forex trading.

BPI-Philamlife: Bancassurance Sales Executive

March,2019-Febuary.,2020

Carry out continuous lead generation. Set appointments whether over the phone or face to face. Conduct financial needs analysis and recommend customized solutions. Strengthen customer relationships. Cross-sell and up-sell BPI-PHILAMLIFE products to BPI customers Establish, maintain, and grow a good relationship with bank partners Prepare submit and analyze sales report on a regular basis